hireology.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy | Hireology

Hireology, Inc. (“Hireology”, “we” or “us”) provides this website (the “Site”) and the resources, services, information, communications, and publications available through the Site (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Site, as well as the associated career websites that we host and make available to you on behalf of our Customers.

To provide some background to individuals who purchase our Services (“Customers”) and their data sources (“Data Sources”), we are a data processor that processes personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) on behalf of and in accordance with the instructions of the data controllers (i.e., our Customers), who may collect such information from Data Sources (typically, candidates) during the recruitment process or otherwise. Our Customers collect such information from Data Sources using the Site. We act only on and in accordance with instructions from the data controllers. The Personal Information from the Data Source(s) is concurrently and automatically stored and backed up from the Site to servers that are under the control and in the possession of our hosting provider. Our data processing activities are limited to the minimum necessary for the performance of the contracts between our Customers and us. For more information regarding how a Data Source’s information is processed, please refer to the applicable Customer’s privacy policy.

### Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure

This Privacy Policy applies to Hireology’s operation and administration of the Site, and to the information that users may provide or that Hireology may have access to through the Site, but not necessarily to the Services.

We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time and Hireology may revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.

All access to and use of the Site and related services and materials is subject to the terms and conditions in [Hireology’s Terms of Use.](https://hireology.com/terms/) Access to and use of the Services are subject to terms and conditions set forth in a separate agreement (“Services Agreement”) between Hireology and the company or other entity purchasing such Services.

The provisions of the Terms of Use and any applicable Services Agreement take precedence over any inconsistent or contrary provisions in this Privacy Policy.

You may withdraw your consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe at [hireology.com](https://hireology.com/)]. Please note that if you do, this Site may suspend its provision of Services to you.

### Personal Information Collected

Hireology collects information from individuals who visit the Site (“Visitors”) and individuals who register to use the Services (“Customers”), including with respect to personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”).

When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services, registering to use the Services, or contacting us for help, Hireology requires you to provide it with contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address (“Required Contact Information”). When purchasing the Services, Hireology requires you to provide it with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Services (“Billing Information”). Hireology may also ask you to provide additional information, such as company annual revenues, number of employees, or industry, or you may offer to provide us with Personal Information during your interaction with the Site (each, “Optional Information”). Required Contact Information, Billing Information, and Optional Information are referred to collectively as “User Data.”

Additionally, User Data you provide to us will be used for your purchases and retained in hard copy form of the original invoice as well as within our database system, which generates our invoices.

### Site Navigational Information

As you navigate Hireology’s Web Site, Hireology may also collect information through the use of commonly used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons. Such information includes standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and browser language), IP address, and the actions you take on the Site (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked). This section describes the types of Site Navigational Information Hireology may collect and how Hireology may use this information.

Hireology uses cookies to make interactions with Hireology’s Site easy and meaningful. When you visit the Site, Hireology’s servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you. They merely recognize your web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to Hireology, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, filling out a web form, or otherwise contacting us, you remain anonymous to Hireology.

There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.

If you have chosen to identify yourself to Hireology, Hireology uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow Hireology to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the Services, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed in your browser. These session cookies allow Hireology to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Services and to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies are required to use the Services.

Hireology uses persistent cookies that only Hireology can read and use to identify browsers that have previously visited the Site. When you purchase the Services or provide Hireology with personal information, a unique identifier is assigned to you. This unique identifier is associated with a persistent cookie that Hireology places on your web browser. Hireology is careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, Hireology does not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. If you disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate Hireology’s Web Site, but you will not be able to successfully use the Services.

Hireology may use information from session and persistent cookies in combination with User Data to provide you with information about Hireology and the Services.

Hireology uses web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about your usage of the Site and interaction with e-mails from Hireology. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular website tied to the web beacon, and a description of a website tied to the web beacon. For example, Hireology may place web beacons in marketing e-mails that notify Hireology when you click on a link in the e-mail that directs you to the Site. Hireology uses web beacons to operate and improve Hireology’s Site and e-mail communications. Hireology may use information from web beacons in combination with User Data to provide you with information about Hireology and the Services.

When you interact with our Site, our servers automatically receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information (“Log Data”). This Log Data is collected passively and may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, Site pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider, the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data and pool it with other information to monitor the use of our Site, and for the technical administration of our Site. We do not associate your IP address with any other Personal Information to identify you personally, except in cases where we are asked to comply with a subpoena or other legal demand or where we suspect that there has been a violation of our policies, our Terms of Use, any applicable Services Agreement or applicable law.

From time-to-time, Hireology engages third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit Hireology’s Site. Hireology may also use other third-party cookies to track the performance of its advertisements. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after Hireology receives it. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of third-party cookies.

If you make a purchase from a third party linked to our Site, the information obtained during your visit to that third party, and the information you give such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to such third party. This is to enable transactions to take place.

Third parties linked to our Site have separate privacy and data collection practices. Hireology has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. For more information regarding the third party, their website, and their privacy policies, please see that merchant’s website.

From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt in to receive information from these third parties, Hireology will (with your permission) share your name and email address with them.

“Personal Information” and “User Data” do not include statistical information. By analyzing your use of our system we may compile certain statistical information, such as anonymous information about how users use our service. Statistical data helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and in order to tailor existing products and services to customer desires. Aggregate statistical information is anonymous and will not be linked to any Personal Information for provision to third parties. We may share such anonymous statistical information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion.

Hireology uses Personal Information and User Data to provide the Services, perform other services requested, to fulfill requests for products, services or information, to communicate with you and to understand your needs. For example, if you request a free trial, Hireology will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Site or the Services.

Hireology may also use Personal Information and User Data for marketing purposes. For example, Hireology may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in Hireology, the Services, and to send you information regarding Hireology and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

Hireology uses credit card information solely to check the financial qualifications of prospective Customers, to collect payment for the Services and to maintain payment records.

Hireology uses Site Navigational Information to operate and improve Hireology’s Web Site. Hireology may also use Site Navigational Information in combination with User Data to provide personalized information about Hireology. In addition to the above, Hireology collects and uses Personal Information and User Data you provide for the following purposes:

  * To comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;
  * To respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of our Site or any product or service on our Site;
  * The protect against legal liability;
  * To protect and defend the rights of Hireology and the services, products, information, and rights of our Site and Services, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the Site and Services;
  * To act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Site users or the public;
  * To identify and resolve technical problems concerning our Site, its information, products and services; and
  * In any other way authorized by you or the applicable user, including as permitted by the Terms of Use and any applicable Services Agreement.

Hireology also uses Personal Information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes. If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the Personal Information they need for the purposes described in this Section, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your Personal Information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

### Disclosure, Processing and Retention

Hireology may share User Data with its agents so that these agents can contact Customers and Visitors who have provided contact information on our behalf. Hireology may also share User Data with its agents to ensure the quality of information provided. Hireology does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

Hireology uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on Hireology’s behalf.We do not sell, rent, or disclose your personal information to anyone else without your permission, except:

  * To someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the purposes listed above under the heading “USE OF INFORMATION”;
  * To Hireology’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, joint venturers, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on our behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;
  * If Hireology has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Hireology’s rights or property, other users of our Site, Services, or other products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and
  * To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including Personal Information, User Data and any other information covered by this Privacy Policy, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, change of control transaction, sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which Hireology or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

### Communications Preferences

You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of Hireology’s marketing e-mails. Additionally, you may send a request specifying your communications preferences to support at [Hireology.com](https://hireology.com/). Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account with Hireology or the Services.

### Correcting and Updating your Information

Customers may update or change their registration information by editing their user or organization record. To update a user profile, please log in to [[https://app.hireology.com](https://app.hireology.com/users/sign_in)] with your Hireology user name and password and click [“Settings/My Info.”] To update an organization’s information, please log in to [[https://app.hireology.com](https://app.hireology.com/)] with your Hireology user name and password and select [“Settings.”] To update Billing Information, please log in to [[https://app.hireology.com](https://app.hireology.com/users/sign_in)] with your Hireology user name and password and select [“Settings/Account.”]. Customers are responsible for informing Hireology about changes to their Customer Information. Hireology will use new or updated Customer Information it receives from Customers to update its own records.

transactional e-mails related to their account with Hireology or the Services.

Hireology will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such User Data except as provided in the applicable Services Agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records of User Data may be viewed or accessed only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the applicable Services Agreement, or as may be required by law. Customers are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their Hireology user names and passwords.

Subject to the Terms of Use and any applicable Services Agreement, Hireology will use commercially reasonable efforts consistent with industry standards to protect User Data from unauthorized access. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. Subject to the Terms of Use and any applicable Services Agreement, Hireology will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of unencrypted electronically stored User Data to affected Customers via email or conspicuous posting on the Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support at [Hireology.com](https://hireology.com/) or by mail at: Hireology Inc., 303 E. Wacker Drive, Suite 400, Chicago, Illinois 60601

Any dispute over privacy or any information described in this Privacy Policy is subject to our Terms of Use and any applicable Services Agreement, including limitations on damages other liability and application of the law of the State of Illinois.

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support at [Hireology.com](https://hireology.com/) or by mail at: Hireology Inc., 303 E. Wacker Drive, Suite 400, Chicago, Illinois 60601
